decoin.io 2019-05-03

# Decoin - Privacy Policy

Last Update : Mar 31, 2019

We at Decoin.io know you care about how your personal information is used and shared, and we’re committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. 

Please read the following to learn more about our Privacy Policy. By using [www.decoin.io](https://decoin.io/) (“Website”) and our services you acknowledge that you accept the practices and policies outlined in this Privacy Policy, and you hereby consent that we will collect, use, and share your information in the following ways. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully as it explains our practices regarding your personal data and how we will treat it, and the basis on which any personal data will be processed by us. We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time so please check this page occasionally to ensure that you’re happy with any changes. 

For the purpose of the applicable data protection legislation (meaning, prior to 25 May 2018 the Data Protection Act 1998 and from 25 May 2018 the General Data Protection Regulation and any legislation which implements it) (the “Data Protection Legislation”), the data controller is DTEP Security OÜ (“Decoin.io”) located of Harju maakond, Tallinn, Lasnamäe linnaosa, Lõõtsa tn 5, Estonia, 11415. 

References in this Privacy and Cookies Policy and on our website to “we”, “our” or “us” are references to DTEP Security OÜ. References to “you” and “your” means each person who interacts with us, uses our website or the products and services we provide. 

###### 1\. Information we collect and process about you

  1. 1.1

We may collect and process the following personal data about you:

    1. 1.1.1

Information you give to us. You may give us information about you when you register on our website [www.decoin.io](https://decoin.io/) or by communicating with us by phone, email or otherwise. This also includes information you provide when you subscribe to any of our services, participate in surveys and user forums, and when you give us any feedback or report a problem with our website. The information you give us may include your name, address, email address, phone number, date of birth, identity documents, username, password, job title and company information. 

    2. 1.1.2

Information we collect about you when you communicate with us by phone, email, post, or otherwise, and when you use our products and services. We collect information such as how and when you contacted us and responded to communications from us and about how and when you use our products and services. 

    3. 1.1.3

Information we collect about you when use our Website or interact with us over the internet, including via social media. Each time you visit our Website or interact with us we may automatically collect the following information: (a) technical information, including the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your device to the Internet, your login information, browser type and version, time zone setting, browser plug-in types and versions, operating system and platform; (b) information about your visit, including the full Uniform Resource Locators (URL); products you viewed or searched for; length of visits to certain pages, page interaction information (such as scrolling, clicks, and mouse-overs); (c) along with our service providers, we may use tracking technologies such as cookies, JavaScript, beacons and Local Storage, which are used to store content information and preferences. 

    4. 1.1.4

Information we collect about you from publicly available sources. This may include information available from social media (depending on your settings and the applicable privacy policies) and information from resources such as Companies House. 

    5. 1.1.5

Information we receive from other sources. We may receive further information about you if you use any of the services we provide. We work closely with third parties (including, for example, suppliers, service providers, identity verification providers) and may receive information about you from them. We may combine information we receive from these other sources with information you give to us and information we collect about you. 

    6. 1.1.6

We may monitor or record telephone conversations or other communications between you and us and keep recordings or transcripts of them and we may keep a copy of any correspondence. 

  2. 1.2

We also collect, use and share aggregated data such as statistical or demographic data. Aggregated data may be derived from your personal data, but it is not considered personal data under the Data Protection Legislation as it does not directly or indirectly identify you. If we combine personal data with non-personal data, the combined data will be treated as Personal Data. 

###### 2\. Cookies

  1. 2.1

We and our service providers collect information about your use of our website from cookies. A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier, which is sent to your browser from a website’s computers and stored on your computer’s hard drive. Once it is it helps analyse website traffic or lets us know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow website applications to respond to you as an individual. The website application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes, and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences. 

  2. 2.2

We use traffic log cookies to identify which of our website pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from our system. 

  3. 2.3

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a customized website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. 

  4. 2.4

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website. 

###### 3\. Purposes and legal basis for using your personal data

  1. 3.1

Where you have requested that we provide a specific product or service to you, or you otherwise make use of those products or services, we will process your personal data in order to perform our contract with you and provide that product or service. 

  2. 3.2

We also use the personal data we hold about you to pursue our legitimate interests in providing and marketing our products and services to you, improving our website, services, and interactions with you and other users of our products and services in the following ways: 
    1. 3.2.1

administer your account and relationship with us and to communicate with you by telephone, mail, email, text (SMS) message, instant messaging or other electronic means; 

    2. 3.2.2

verify your identity and detect fraud and crime and comply with any legal or regulatory requirements; 

    3. 3.2.3

provide you with information about the products and services that you request from us; 

    4. 3.2.4

provide you with information about other products and services we offer that are similar to those that you have already purchased or enquired about; 

    5. 3.2.5

provide you with information about products or services we feel may interest you or be best for you; 

    6. 3.2.6

your data may be shared with product or service providers to validate if you are an existing customer (which may affect whether you can be accepted for one of their products) or for fraud prevention purposes. The product or service provider does not have permission to use these data for any other purpose including marketing. 

    7. 3.2.7

notify you about changes to our services; 

    8. 3.2.8

ensure that content from our website is presented in the most effective manner for you and your device; 

    9. 3.2.9

to administer our website and for internal operations, including troubleshooting, data analysis, testing, research, statistical and survey purposes; 

    10. 3.2.10

to build up a picture of your interests so that you don’t miss information relevant to you when you visit our website; 

    11. 3.2.11

to improve the service we offer you and to try and ensure that you get the best from our website; 

    12. 3.2.12

to allow you to participate in interactive features of our website and services; 

    13. 3.2.13

as part of our efforts to keep our website safe and secure; 

    14. 3.2.14

to measure the effectiveness of advertising we serve to you and others, and to deliver relevant advertising to you; 

    15. 3.2.15

to send direct marketing to you 

    16. 3.2.16

to make suggestions and recommendations about products or services that we think may be of interest based on usage patterns both on our website and on other channels (such as email and social media); 

    17. 3.2.17

for training and quality purposes; 

    18. 3.2.18

to check any instructions you give to us and for the purposes of investigating any complaint you may make, or as evidence in any dispute or anticipated disputes between you and us. 

  3. 3.3

In some cases we may also use the personal data we hold about you to comply with our legal obligations or enter into or perform a contract with you. 

###### 4\. Who your data can be disclosed to

  1. 4.1

We may need to disclose your data to others to ensure the effective provision to you of the products, services, and information you request. Your data may also be disclosed to the other entities as described below 

  2. 4.2

We may share your personal information with any member of our group. We currently only have subsidiaries, but from time to time this may also include any holding company we have and their subsidiaries. 

  3. 4.3

We may share your information with selected third parties including: 
    1. 4.3.1

Suppliers, service providers, business partners, and sub-contractors; 

    2. 4.3.2

Fraud prevention agencies, to prevent crime and trace those responsible; 

    3. 4.3.3

Identity verification providers, to comply with legal or regulatory requirements; 

    4. 4.3.4

Analytics and search engine providers that assist us in the improvement and optimisation of our website; 

    5. 4.3.5

IT and software providers who supply us with our IT infrastructure for the provision of our services and administering our business (including our internal and external communications) and who also help us manage our customer and contact databases, customer relationships and marketing. 

  4. 4.4

We may disclose your personal information to third parties if: 
    1. 4.4.1

we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we may disclose your personal data to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets; 

    2. 4.4.2

DTEP Security OU or substantially all of its assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal data held by it about its customers will be one of the transferred assets; and 

    3. 4.4.3

we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply any contract with you and other agreements; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of our business, our customers, or others. 

  5. 4.5

We review all our relationships with third parties carefully so that we can be sure as possible that their practices match our own commitments to you relating to privacy and security. We also comply with the Data Protection Legislation in our dealings with these third parties to ensure that your information is appropriately protected. 

###### 5\. Marketing & Testing Purposes

  1. 5.1

We may use your Personal Data (such as your email address or phone number). We may also send you promotional material concerning our services or our partners’ services (which we believe may interest you), including but not limited to, by building an automated profile based on your Personal Data, for marketing purposes. You may choose not to receive our promotional or marketing emails by clicking on the “unsubscribe” link in the emails that you receive from us. Please note that even if you unsubscribe from our newsletter, we may continue to send you service-related updates and notifications or reply to your queries and feedback you provide us. 

  2. 5.2

We may send direct marketing communications to you, including by email, telephone or SMS or mail. If we are required by law to have your consent to do this then we will only do so if we have that consent. 

  3. 5.3

From time to time, we may conduct surveys or test features, and analyze the data we have to develop, evaluate and improve these features, all in order to improve our Services and think of new and exciting features for our users. 

###### 6\. Where we store and transfer your data

  1. 6.1

Where we store your information ourselves it is stored on our secure servers in the EU. However, where we share your information with third parties this may involve transferring it to a country outside the EU and the European Economic Area (EEA). This may include countries that do not have data protection laws which are as strong as those in the UK or EU. Where we do this we will take the steps required under the Data Protection Legislation to ensure that your information is appropriately protected. If you would like any further information about this then please contact us using the details in the Contact section below. 

  2. 6.2

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our website; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use appropriate procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access, loss or damage. 

###### 7\. Retention

  1. 7.1

We will retain your Personal Data for as long as necessary to provide our services, and as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our policies. Retention periods will be determined taking into account the type of information that is collected and the purpose for which it is collected, bearing in mind the requirements applicable to the situation and the need to destroy outdated, unused information at the earliest reasonable time. Under applicable regulations, we will keep records containing client personal data, trading information, account opening documents, communications and anything else as required by applicable laws and regulations. 

###### 8\. Third party websites

  1. 8.1

Our website may contain links to other websites. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these websites or their policies. Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites. 

###### 9\. How we protect your information

  1. 9.1

We have implemented administrative, technical, and physical safeguards to help prevent unauthorized access, use, or disclosure of your Personal Data. Your data is stored on secure servers and isn’t publicly available. We limit access of your information only to those employees or partners on a “need to know” basis, in order to enable the carrying out of the agreement between us. 

  2. 9.2

While we seek to protect your information to ensure that it is kept confidential, we cannot absolutely guarantee its security. You need to help us prevent unauthorized access to your account by protecting your password appropriately and limiting access to your account. You will be solely responsible for keeping your password confidential and for all use of your password and your account, including any unauthorized use. You should also be aware that there is always some risk involved in transmitting information over the internet. While we strive to protect your Personal Data, we cannot ensure or warrant the security and privacy of your Personal Data or other content you transmit using the service, and you do so at your own risk. 

###### 10\. Your rights

  1. 10.1

Under the Data Protection Legislation, you have certain rights in respect of the personal data we hold about you. These may include rights to: receive confirmation as to whether or not Personal Data concerning you is being processed, and access your stored Personal Data, together with supplementary information, receive a copy of Personal Data you directly volunteer to us in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format; request rectification of your Personal Data that is in our control; request erasure of your Personal Data; Object to the processing of Personal Data by us; request to restrict processing of your Personal Data by us; lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority.   
These rights are limited in some situations. For example, if we have a legal requirement or a compelling legitimate ground we may continue to process your data even where you request its deletion. 

  2. 10.2

If you would like to exercise any of these rights, please contact us using the details in the Contact section below. 

  3. 10.3

You also have the right to make a complaint if you feel your personal data has been mishandled. We would encourage you to contact us in the first instance. 

###### 11\. Changes to our privacy and cookie policy

  1. 11.1

Any changes we may make to our Privacy and Cookie Policy in the future will be posted on this page and, where we consider it appropriate, notified to you by email. Please check back frequently to see any updates or changes to our Privacy and Cookie Policy. 

###### 12\. Contact

  1. Questions, comments and requests regarding this Privacy and Cookie Policy should be addressed to info@decoin.io. 

### Welcome to Decoin Exchange

We are only accepting signups of limited invited accounts at this stage. Subscribe below to request early access to the platform

Still don't own any Decoin? [Click here](https://dtep.decoin.io/)
